[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest crop for the Americas?", "correct_answer": "Corn", "incorrect_answers": ["Wheat", "Soybeans", "Milo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1992 movie, starring Geena Davis and Madonna, centers on a group of women trying to start a female baseball team.", "correct_answer": "A League of Their Own", "incorrect_answers": ["BABE Ruths", "The Sandlot", "Angels in the Outfield"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pandas do not hibernate.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which general born in New York in 1954 was elected the 10th Commander of the U.S. Central Command?", "correct_answer": "David Petraeus", "incorrect_answers": ["George Patton", "Lloyd Wright", "Wesley Clark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these scenes is unique for the 2004 movie The Passion Of The Christ, making it different from the traditional story of the Passion?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The crucified thief who mocks at Jesus has his eye pecked out by a crow.", "Judas Iscariot is tormented by demons who appear as children to him.", "In the Garden of Gethsemane Jesus speaks with the Devil and crushes a snake under his foot."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Spiderman is the alter ego of Jonah Jameson.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animal is the venomous Gila monster that is indigenous to southwestern United States and northern Mexico?", "correct_answer": "Lizard", "incorrect_answers": ["Invertebrate", "Frog", "Mammal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Oscar-winning actor portrayed Michael Corleone in The Godfather trilogy?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Pesci", "Ashton Cutcher", "Russel Crowe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 8 Mile, Eminem plays a character nicknamed B-Rabbit. What is B-Rabbits real name?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Jimmy Doring", "Jimmy Jones", "Jimmy Panella"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which U.S. state is the Multnomah Falls located?", "correct_answer": "Oregon", "incorrect_answers": ["Ohio", "Maine", "Missouri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animal is the largest of the deer family and can be found in the northern parts of North America.", "correct_answer": "Moose", "incorrect_answers": ["Gazelle", "White Tailed Deer", "Elk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These cetaceans live off the southern coast of South America and can be found up to 150 miles (240 km) up the Amazon River. They are colored pale blue with a white underside. What is their name?", "correct_answer": "Tuxici", "incorrect_answers": ["Amazon dolphin", "South American dolphin", "Franciscana"]}]